[
    {
        "question": "What is the result of 8514 multiplied by 3978?",
        "answer": "33868692"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the result of 7739 multiplied by 5807?",
        "answer": "44940373"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the result of 3024 multiplied by 3512?",
        "answer": "10620288"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the result of 9248 multiplied by 8489?",
        "answer": "78506272"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the result of 2614 multiplied by 1787?",
        "answer": "4671218"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the result of 8560 multiplied by 7560?",
        "answer": "64713600"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the result of 3471 multiplied by 8414?",
        "answer": "29204994"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the result of 9123 multiplied by 1242?",
        "answer": "11330766"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the result of 4481 multiplied by 9922?",
        "answer": "44460482"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the result of 2217 multiplied by 1042?",
        "answer": "2310114"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the result of 6316 multiplied by 2003?",
        "answer": "12650948"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the result of 5131 multiplied by 1458?",
        "answer": "7480998"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the result of 3578 multiplied by 4381?",
        "answer": "15675218"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the result of 4660 multiplied by 6092?",
        "answer": "28388720"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the result of 5640 multiplied by 8755?",
        "answer": "49378200"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the result of 6671 multiplied by 3578?",
        "answer": "23868838"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the result of 2243 multiplied by 4065?",
        "answer": "9117795"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the result of 6424 multiplied by 7905?",
        "answer": "50781720"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the result of 5072 multiplied by 4473?",
        "answer": "22687056"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the result of 2338 multiplied by 7136?",
        "answer": "16683968"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the result of 4329 multiplied by 3368?",
        "answer": "14580072"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the result of 2442 multiplied by 8796?",
        "answer": "21479832"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the result of 7826 multiplied by 5437?",
        "answer": "42549962"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the result of 5373 multiplied by 6283?",
        "answer": "33758559"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the result of 2172 multiplied by 4132?",
        "answer": "8974704"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the result of 3421 multiplied by 9007?",
        "answer": "30812947"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the result of 6737 multiplied by 7842?",
        "answer": "52831554"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the result of 5726 multiplied by 3505?",
        "answer": "20069630"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the result of 8222 multiplied by 9984?",
        "answer": "82088448"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the result of 9408 multiplied by 2362?",
        "answer": "22221696"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the result of 8730 multiplied by 6775?",
        "answer": "59145750"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the result of 6698 multiplied by 7305?",
        "answer": "48928890"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the result of 5539 multiplied by 1183?",
        "answer": "6552637"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the result of 9121 multiplied by 2909?",
        "answer": "26532989"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the result of 8737 multiplied by 7860?",
        "answer": "68672820"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the result of 5599 multiplied by 3027?",
        "answer": "16948173"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the result of 8617 multiplied by 9368?",
        "answer": "80724056"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the result of 5679 multiplied by 9707?",
        "answer": "55126053"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the result of 8143 multiplied by 2436?",
        "answer": "19836348"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the result of 2687 multiplied by 4020?",
        "answer": "10801740"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the result of 1012 multiplied by 9599?",
        "answer": "9714188"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the result of 2424 multiplied by 6319?",
        "answer": "15317256"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the result of 3529 multiplied by 3688?",
        "answer": "13014952"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the result of 4312 multiplied by 5299?",
        "answer": "22849288"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the result of 5765 multiplied by 2415?",
        "answer": "13922475"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the result of 5319 multiplied by 3373?",
        "answer": "17940987"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the result of 9295 multiplied by 4814?",
        "answer": "44746130"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the result of 8891 multiplied by 5575?",
        "answer": "49567325"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the result of 4254 multiplied by 5319?",
        "answer": "22627026"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the result of 5900 multiplied by 5062?",
        "answer": "29865800"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the result of 7751 multiplied by 8705?",
        "answer": "67472455"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the result of 9712 multiplied by 1674?",
        "answer": "16257888"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the result of 2582 multiplied by 3240?",
        "answer": "8365680"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the result of 6183 multiplied by 1831?",
        "answer": "11321073"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the result of 3448 multiplied by 1904?",
        "answer": "6564992"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the result of 4319 multiplied by 8988?",
        "answer": "38819172"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the result of 1071 multiplied by 6379?",
        "answer": "6831909"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the result of 8797 multiplied by 7532?",
        "answer": "66259004"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the result of 1401 multiplied by 4177?",
        "answer": "5851977"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the result of 2724 multiplied by 3398?",
        "answer": "9256152"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the result of 6949 multiplied by 3426?",
        "answer": "23807274"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the result of 2413 multiplied by 8520?",
        "answer": "20558760"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the result of 3790 multiplied by 8733?",
        "answer": "33098070"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the result of 9403 multiplied by 8419?",
        "answer": "79163857"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the result of 2176 multiplied by 9716?",
        "answer": "21142016"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the result of 8836 multiplied by 9849?",
        "answer": "87025764"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the result of 3154 multiplied by 9625?",
        "answer": "30357250"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the result of 4157 multiplied by 3415?",
        "answer": "14196155"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the result of 2383 multiplied by 8293?",
        "answer": "19762219"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the result of 7369 multiplied by 9946?",
        "answer": "73292074"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the result of 3684 multiplied by 2043?",
        "answer": "7526412"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the result of 4808 multiplied by 1589?",
        "answer": "7639912"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the result of 7313 multiplied by 3286?",
        "answer": "24030518"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the result of 6700 multiplied by 7209?",
        "answer": "48300300"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the result of 6580 multiplied by 7634?",
        "answer": "50231720"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the result of 2152 multiplied by 3868?",
        "answer": "8323936"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the result of 6996 multiplied by 3154?",
        "answer": "22065384"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the result of 4182 multiplied by 5388?",
        "answer": "22532616"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the result of 6650 multiplied by 8865?",
        "answer": "58952250"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the result of 8947 multiplied by 9587?",
        "answer": "85774889"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the result of 7978 multiplied by 5155?",
        "answer": "41126590"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the result of 9209 multiplied by 7847?",
        "answer": "72263023"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the result of 6243 multiplied by 3160?",
        "answer": "19727880"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the result of 7304 multiplied by 7216?",
        "answer": "52705664"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the result of 2197 multiplied by 3005?",
        "answer": "6601985"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the result of 2167 multiplied by 1065?",
        "answer": "2307855"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the result of 3185 multiplied by 5680?",
        "answer": "18090800"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the result of 6136 multiplied by 2692?",
        "answer": "16518112"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the result of 4548 multiplied by 6711?",
        "answer": "30521628"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the result of 8872 multiplied by 6740?",
        "answer": "59797280"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the result of 1314 multiplied by 5885?",
        "answer": "7732890"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the result of 6173 multiplied by 4767?",
        "answer": "29426691"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the result of 5895 multiplied by 6837?",
        "answer": "40304115"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the result of 2561 multiplied by 6901?",
        "answer": "17673461"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the result of 4070 multiplied by 3277?",
        "answer": "13337390"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the result of 4226 multiplied by 8864?",
        "answer": "37459264"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the result of 1388 multiplied by 1941?",
        "answer": "2694108"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the result of 3783 multiplied by 4154?",
        "answer": "15714582"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the result of 3929 multiplied by 2847?",
        "answer": "11185863"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the result of 5239 multiplied by 4683?",
        "answer": "24534237"
    }
]